evolvehq.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy — Evolve

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 1st, 2012. 

This policy explains our information practices, defines your privacy options and describes how your information is collected and used by Echobit LLC ("Echobit"), the operator of this website (evolvehq.com; the "Site"). 

This Site, the Evolve client software (the “Software”) and the APIs developed by Echobit (the "APIs") allow you to play games with your friends, meet and play with new friends, chat with fellow gamers, track your playtime and achievements across thousands of games, and share game-related media content. 

This privacy policy will address the information you provide us or that we collect when you visit or use this Site, use our Software or provide information through the APIs. 

By using visiting the Site, the Software or the APIs you agree to the collection and use of information in the manner described in this policy. Echobit shall have right at any time and without prior notice, at its sole discretion, to revise this policy. Such revisions and additions shall be effective immediately upon notice, which may be given by any means, including but not limited to posting the revised or additional terms and conditions on the Site. You are responsible for reviewing the Site periodically for any modification to this policy. 

####  Information We Collect 

You will most likely provide us personal information to us when you register as a Site user, download and use the Software or use our APIs. The personal information we collect may include: user ID, password, your name, your address, your email address, and your phone number. 

The information you submit to Echobit may also include text, images, videos, music, software in addition to any other materials you might submit as part of, or in conjunction with, your use of the Site. 

####  Messaging and Sharing 

The Site, Software and APIs may allow you to access and use blogs, forums, status updates, realtime text and voice chat, and other message areas. As part of your use of the Site, the Software or APIs you may elect to share with your friends: activity feed events, comments, ratings, avatars, forum posts and topics, status updates, screenshots, videos, and playtime history. By accessing the Site's settings dashboard, you may decide which of your friends you want to share such information with. 

Game forums and the Site's public forums can be viewed by all. Please keep this in mind when posting information to these forums. In addition, your avatar and basic profile data may be viewed by anyone, subject to your currently selected privacy settings. 

####  Other Collected Data 

In addition to the personal information you supply, we collect certain information to evaluate how visitors, guests, and members use the Site or Software. We collect data to make our service work better for you in the following ways: to improve the design of the Site, Software or APIs, to provide personalization and to evaluate the performance of our marketing programs. Data gathered for these purposes may include IP addresses, cookies, browser user agents, operating system and software version, client logs, installation logs, access timestamps, and system fingerprints. 

In addition to the above collection of data, we can collect, with your permission, account credentials for certain third party services (e.g. Steam, AIM, MSN, PSN, ICQ, and so on) as part of our efforts to let you show your comprehensive gaming history unified via your Site profile. 

####  How We Use Information 

Our primary goal in collecting your customer information is to provide you with a personalized, relevant, and positive experience with the Site and Software. 

You can register on the Site to receive promotions and updates, or to be contacted for market research purposes. The contact information you submit will not be used for these purposes unless you specifically opt-in. You can control your privacy settings regarding such marketing communications (see the section below entitled "How to Access or Correct Your Information"). 

From time to time, you may be invited to participate in optional customer surveys or promotions, and Echobit may request that you provide some or all of the above listed personal information in those surveys or promotions. We use information collected from surveys to learn about our customers in order to improve our services and develop new products and services of interest to our customers. 

Echobit may use information provided by you and collected about you to facilitate a better experience on our website and to give us useful business information. 

####  Our Commitment to Data Security 

Access to your personal data is limited to authorized Echobit staff or approved vendors. Although total security does not exist on the Internet, Echobit shall make commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard the information that you submit to Echobit. 

####  Echobit Communications 

When you sign up as a registered user, you may elect to have Echobit provide you with marketing communications such as email newsletters, product and service updates, and promotions. Our customers generally find this type of information useful. If you do not want to continue to receive such communications, you can click on the unsubscribe links made available to you in the footers of these emails or visit the preferences dashboard on the Evolve website. 

####  Your Information and Echobit Service Providers 

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, website hosting and maintenance, customer relationship management, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data. 

####  How to Access or Correct Your Information 

You can access and maintain your personally identifiable information on the settings dashboard of the Evolve website. To protect your privacy and security, we require a user ID and password to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

####  Disclosure and Use of Information 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process. It is also possible that Echobit would sell all or substantially all of its assets and business. In any transaction of this kind, customer information, including your personally identifiable information, may be among the assets that are transferred. If we decide to so transfer your personally identifiable information, you will be notified by email or by a post to the Site. In addition, we reserve the right to collect, store, maintain, analyze and disclose to third parties all non-personally identifiable information concerning (1) your use of the Site, (2) your use of the Software and (3) any other information you might post to the Site or submit separately to Echobit. 

####  Links to Other Websites 

The Site may contain links to other websites. Echobit is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each web site that collects personally identifiable information. Some linked sites may be co-branded with our Evolve trademarks and those of our business partners. They may have the look and feel of evolvehq.com, but the URL in your browser window will indicate that you are visiting a different site. This policy only applies to information collected by Echobit. 

####  How to Contact Us 

Should you have privacy questions or concerns, please send an email to contact {at} evolvehq.com.
